

Ivan Zabrodin

E-mail : xvanx84@gmail.com Website: https://ivanzabrodin.com

Phone: +79119423159 Address: Belgrade, Serbia

Work experience

Paycos 12.05.2020 — Present

Software Engineer

Payment system development, API integration.

International payment system based on PCI DSS standard.

Microservices. NATS.

Antifraud integration.

Crypto wallet.

Molinos 20.09.2017 — 30.04.2020

Ruby on Rails Developer

Creating web applications on RubyOnRails

Working with API / using and creating / with full documentation

Building a project architecture

Assessing the amount and timing of tasks for the backend

Querying the database (PostgreSQL)

Implementation of VK, Telegram, Facebook Messenger and Viber bots

CashCowPro 25.02.2017 — 31.05.2018

Software Developer

Project: Analytics platform and software tool for online sellers (https://www.cashcowpro.com/)

Responsible for a part of developing highly distributed Ruby on Rails web application for a high performance, high traffic, advanced interactive site that attracts a lot of visitors per day, by providing technical documentation for various products online.

Brabens Development

04.05.2016 - 15.02.2017

Ruby on Rails Developer

Projects:

Search For Manuals Online

Search For Alternative apps Online

Back-end developing using Ruby on Rails, implementing parsers and crawlers.

Ivan Zabrodin 1

Qualifications

Summary:

Software development engineer featuring expertise in Ruby on Rails / Go, web frameworks, and other programming languages, a passion for Web 2.0 trends, APIs, mashups, and other disruptive technologies.

- Strong knowledge of Web standards and protocols
- Understanding of relation model and its implementations
- Knowledge of RESTful API
- Writing technical documentation

Technical skills:

Front-end: HTML5/CSS3, JS, Sass, Slim, JQuery, Bootstrap

Back-end: Ruby(Ruby on Rails, Sinatra), Go, RDBMS (MySQL, PostgreSQL), RSpec, Nginx, Puma, Redis, Sidekiq,

Docker

Cloud infrastructure systems: Heroku, AWS

Tools: Vim, Jira, Trello, Slack

Version control: Git

Automating software building: Bundler, Capistrano, Rake

Core principles:

- Follow the CS/software design principles
- Design before implementation
- The team is greater than any single person
- Testing leads to stable maintainable code

Language Skills:

- Russian Native
- English Intermediate

Education

Ruby on Rails developer

Dec 2015 — Mar 2016

GeekBrains

https://geekbrains.ru/

Ruby on Rails developer

Apr 2017 — Aug 2017

mkdev

https://mkdev.me/

Interests

- Snowboard, surfing, skateboarding, workouts
- Foreign languages learning

References

References available upon request.

Ivan Zabrodin 2